<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Article>
    <Title>Best Practices</Title>
    <MenuTitle>Best Practices</MenuTitle>
    <Content>
<![CDATA[
<h2>Recommendation to developers</h2>
<p>Add the name of the webshop to the HTTP header "User-Agent", when you send a request to the service. Preferably also the name of webshop provider if applicable.</p>
<p>If you have a registered user at fraktguide.bring.no, please also include XML API's Public ID parameter in the query.
This makes it possible for us to send any relevant messages via the registered e-mail address.</p>
<h2>Error Handling</h2>
<p>NB! Remember to use timeout and error handling when making requests to the service. Handle errors in a way that is satisfactory for your online store, see <a href="/learn/shipping-guide/introduction/errorcodes.html">Error codes</a>.</p>
<h2>Error Handling Strategies:</h2>
<p>Use the """offline data to calculate price, or</p>
<p>Set a fixed standard price of the package</p>
<p>Note that if a package is out of coverage area or are too big / heavy to send, the Shipping Guide may not offer any products for sending and thus gives an empty answer set. Remember to add a default handling of this case.<p>
<h2>XML Schema Versioning</h2>
<p>
    Fraktguiden makes an effort to always be backwards compatible regarding dataformat for requests and responses of the Web Service.
</p>
<p>
    To achieve this, a <b>SchemaVersion</b> element is used in the request, indicating which version the client is on and
    what dataformat the client expects in the result.
    We make an effort not to return new elements in the response when an old schema version is specified.
</p>
<p>
    When changes in the schema are made, the SchemaVersion is incremented by one.
    The new schema is used at the <b>same endpoint URL</b> as before and uses the same namespace for its XML elements.
    A TraceMessage element (info message) in the
    response is added to inform the client that its schema should be updated. Old schema versions might in the future be unsupported.
</p>
<p>
    Regarding the XML API (not Web Services), an XML Schema is not used at all. Therefore, clients of the XML API is
    expected to handle new elements that appear. Nevertheless, the response will be backwards compatible in that elements are not renamed or deleted.
</p>

<p class="exampleLink">
    <a href="/fraktguide/ws/fraktguide-latest.wsdl" target="_blank">WSDL</a> (latest schema version)
</p>
<p>
    It is also possible to download specific WSDL / schema versions:
    <a href="/fraktguide/ws/fraktguide-v1.wsdl" target="_blank">1</a>,
    <a href="/fraktguide/ws/fraktguide-v2.wsdl" target="_blank">2</a>,
    <a href="/fraktguide/ws/fraktguide-v3.wsdl" target="_blank">3</a>,
    <a href="/fraktguide/ws/fraktguide-v4.wsdl" target="_blank">4</a>.
    Current version is 4.
</p>
<p class="exampleLink">
    <a href="/fraktguide/schemaDoc.do" target="_blank">Fraktguide XML Schema documentation</a>
</p>

]]>
    </Content>
</Article>