<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Article>
    <Ingress>Shippingguide (Fraktguiden) is a free service from Bring that allows you to calculate prices, time estimations, product information and environmental information (and more).</Ingress>
    <MenuTitle>Introduction to Shipping Guide API</MenuTitle>
    <Content>
<![CDATA[

<p>
    <a target="_blank" href="http://fraktguide.bring.no/fraktguide/demoVelgFraktalternativ.do?from=7600&to=1473&weightInGrams=1800&length=10&width=20&height=30&product=servicepakke&product=pa_doren&product=bpakke_dor-dor&product=a-post&callbackUrl=http://fraktguide.bring.no/fraktguide/popupCallback.jsp">Demo!</a> (Norwegian)
</p>

<p>The data is available using different integration methods. Choose the option that fits your need best</p>

<h2>XML</h2>
<p>
	XML API is the easiest way to integrate the Shipping Guide to an online store. The method provides access to data from Bring via a single interface.</p>
<p>
	<a href="./documentation/apireference.html">API Reference</a>
</p>

<h2>JSON / JSONP</h2>
<p>
   	Web browsers can retrieve information from external sites if the data are made available in JSONP format.
	The purpose is that you can paste HTML / Javascript on your web page and easily use data from the Shipping guide without server components on your web page.
</p>
<p>
	<a href="./documentation/apireference.html">API Reference</a>
</p>

<h2>Web Services</h2>
<p>
	With Online Web Services, you can look up price, transportation, area coverage and product information for each product as required.
	For advanced users we recommend the Web Services with several options in the query.
</p>
<p>
    <a href="./documentation/webservices.html">How to use Web Services</a>
</p>

<h2> Offline data (manual download and Web Service) </h2>
<p>
     This is pre-prepared data for offline use.
     Enter the zip code you are sending from and which products you want data for. For each product you get:
</p>
<p>
    <a href="./documentation/offlinedata.html">More information about offline data</a>
</p>


]]>
    </Content>
</Article>